http://www.optp.com/privacy-policy

888.819.0121
Sign In
OPTP (Orthopedic Physical Therapy Products)
0
OPTP (Orthopedic Physical Therapy Products)
New Customers: Register For An Account
Please sign up if this is your first visit to our web site.
Register
Returning Customers: Sign In
Please sign in if you are a returning customer.
Close X
Professional
I'm a healthcare/fitness professional and would like exclusive Professional pricing.
Create Account
Distributor
I'm a distributor of healthcare/fitness products and would like exclusive Distributor pricing.
Create Account
888.819.0121
CART (0)
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information from that point forward, not retroactively. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example, to add you to one of our mailing lists.
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may Contact Us or call 888.819.0121.
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
OPTP respects your right to privacy. Keeping customer information secure and only using it to assist our customer's satisfaction is important to OPTP. The personally identifiable information we collect from you such as name, address, e-mail, telephone numbers, fax numbers, and credit card information is not shared with any external sources, unless we have authorization from you and/or is required to do so by law.
OPTP adheres to strict standards of security to safeguard any personally identifiable information our customers share with us.
The collection and use of any personally identifiable information is only used to deliver superior service and to meet the requirements needed to administrate our business effectively (i.e., responding to customer inquiries, processing orders, facilitating payment, customer mailings and distribution of catalogs).
Only trained, authorized employees are permitted to handle the customer's personally identifiable information.
We use state of the art technology to protect your data when you shop our website. OPTP uses Secure Socket Layer Software (SSL) to protect your data from being received by third parties. SSL encrypts all the personally identifiable information including your name, address, and credit card information as it transmits over the Internet.
OPTP provides links to several other sites for the benefit of our customers to receive helpful information and services. OPTP is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of linked sites, as they are not controlled by OPTP. Please contact linked sites to become familiar with their privacy policies.
OPTP has no intention to collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. Parental permission is necessary for children under the age of 13 to submit personally identifiable information. OPTP will instruct children under the age of 13 not to submit personally identifiable information.
OPTP reserves the rights to make change to the terms of this privacy policy at any time. A revised policy will be posted on our website. We encourage anyone who has questions or comments regarding the above Privacy Policy or your specific personally identifiable information to send an e-mail to us at optp@optp.com or call 763.553.0452.
If you have submitted personally identifiable information to OPTP electronically and would like it removed or modified, please contact us and we will use every reasonable effort to comply with your request.
Categories
Therapy
Fitness
Innovators
Education
Service & Support
Contact Us
About Us
Sku:
Availability:
View Details
Video
